JAN CZIZIKOW



PERSONAL DETAILS

- **□** 12 June 1992
- [□] +(86) 131-6700-7112
- □ jan_czizikow@hotmail.com
- www.janczizikow.com

PROFILE

Currently a senior undergraduate business student in Donghua University, living in China since 2012. Passionate about marketing, PR, branding and serious about future career in related business field. Highly motivated, proactive and adaptable fast-learner, eager to further develop his skills through a challenging experience. Believing that education is based on two pillars: theory and practice, he engaged in a couple of part-time positions through studies.

EXPERIENCE

Social Cloud China

Full & Part-time / 1 year July 2015 - May 2016

Winwho Technology

Part-time / 4 months March 2015 - June 2015

Fujian Hotel

Full-time / 2 months July 2014 - 2014 August

Marketing Assistant

- Assisted in developing marketing campaigns
- Assisted in organizing events and press conferences
- Created and maintained relationships and partnerships with media and sponsors
- Organized and attended meetings with clients and potential partners
- Compiled reports and marketing materials (newsletters, social media content, press releases, brochures, posters)

Event Marketing Intern

- Assisted in planning, organizing and implementation of online and offline events
- Product and brand promotion via public relation activities
- Edited, maitaned and updated "财神所聘 / Caishen Locksreen" app wallpapers

Hotel Guest Relation Officer

- Offered assistance and provided needed or sought information to the guests
- Solicited guest responses, concerning their satisfaction and complaints
- Conducted inspections of the lobby, monitored officers, reported unusual occurrences, handled lost-and-found matters

EDUCATION

Donghua University, China

2014 - Present

Beijing Language and Culture University, China

2012 - 2014

Bachelor of Business Administration

- GPA 3.2/ 4.0
- English-taught Business degree with Chinese courses

Chinese Language Studies

- Mastered 2,500 commonly used words and related grammar patterns
- Passed HSK5 with a total score of 235/300 06.2014

SKILLS & EXPERTISE

Languages

Polish: Native Russian: Bilingual English: Fluent

Chinese (Mandarin): Proficient

Knowledge

Social Media Marketing Marketing Communications Public Relations

Technical

Microsof Office: Advanced HTML5 & CSS3: Intermediate Adobe Photoshop: Basic Adobe Illustrator: Basic

Interests

Traveling Skateboarding Digital Marketing & Web Design

REFEREES

Ambra Schillirò

Director of Social Cloud
□ +(86) 158-2112-2831
□ ambra.schilliro@socialcloudchina.com

Marko Ljubičič

Professor at Donghua University

□ (+86) 150-2124-2364

□ mr.ljubicic@gmail.com